var questions =[
    {
        num : 1,
        question : "Which of the following is an example of DML?",
        answer : "UPDATE",
        options : [
            "CREATE",
            "UPDATE",
            "DROP",
            "ALTER "
        ]
    },
    {
num: 2,
question: "Network that covers geographic areas that are larger, such as districts or cities is",
answer: "MAN",
options: [
"LAN",
"MAN",
"WAN",
"none of the above"
]
},
{
num: 3,
question: "What is divide by 0 in Javascript?    \nvar a = 10;    \nvar b = 0;\ndocument.write(a/b);",
answer: "Infinity is printed",
options: [
"Nothing is printed",
"0 is printed",
"Infinity is printed",
"Some Garbage Value"
]
},

{
num: 4,
question: "FILE is of type... ... ...",
answer: "struct type",
options: [
"int type",
"char * type",
"struct type",
"None of them"
]
},
{
num: 5,
question: "..is a process where you show only relevant data and hide unnecessary details of an object from the user.",
answer: "Abstraction",
options: [
"Abstraction",
"Polymorphism",
"Inheritance",
"Encapsulation"
]
},
{
    num: 6,
    question: "In the ... ... ... transmission mode, communication is bidirectional",
    answer: "full-duplex.",
    options: [
    "Simplex",
    "Half-duplex",
    "full-duplex",
    "hybrid"
    ]
    },
    {
        num: 7,
        question: "Which of the following is not a proper file operation mode?",
        answer: "append",
        options: [
        "close",
        "read",
        "write",
        "append"
        ]
        },
        {
            num: 8,
            question: "In this Phase the software is checks for bugs and verifies its performance before delivery to users.",
            answer: "Software routines",
            options: [
            "Requirement Collection",
            "Design",
            "Development",
            "Testing"
            ]
            },
            {
                num: 9,
                question: "IaaS stands for",
                answer: "Infrastructure as a service",
                options: [
                "Internet as a service",
                "Infrastructure as a service",
                "Boath a and b",
                "All of the above"
                ]
                },
                {
                    num: 10,
                    question: "PHP refers to",
                    answer: " Hypertext Preprocessor",
                    options: [
                    "Hyper High Program",
                    "Hypertext Preprocessor",
                    "Hyper Preprocessor",
                    "Hypertext Processor"
                    ]
                    },
                    
            
];